ashakumara.com 2019-02-23

# Asha Kumara - Sexy Indian Teen!

**Introduction**

This Privacy Policy Statement sets forth the policies and practices with respect to information or data gathered regarding subscriber and members of this site. This is an adult site that expressly and strictly limits its membership to adults. All persons under the age of 18 are strictly prohibited from accessing or viewing the contents of this site.

This site does not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons under the age of 18.

Notice - Use of website by the subscriber constitutes the subscriber's express assent to the use of personal information collected by site.

CAREFULLY READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT BECAUSE BY YOUR SUBSCRIPTION TO AND USE OF THIS SITE YOU WILL BE EXPRESSLY SIGNIFYING THAT YOU AGREE TO THIS POLICY STATEMENT AND THAT YOU ASSENT TO THE USE OF ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT YOU SUPPLY OR THAT IS COLLECTED ABOUT YOU AS DETAILED IN THIS POLICY STATEMENT.

IF YOU DO NOT EXPRESSLY AGREE WITH ALL OF THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT YOU SHOULD NOT SUBSCRIBE TO OR USE THIS SITE.

What Information About Subscribers is Collected?

When any adult consumer signs-on as a member or subscriber of this site that consumer will be required to provide certain personal as well as demographic information which may include the subscriber's name, e-mail address, zip code, country, username, and password. This site collects any and all such information and includes it in its customer database.

If the site features or conducts any special events, special promotions or offers, contests or polls, a subscriber of the site may be asked to provide information in order to participate, if the subscriber voluntarily provides that information, all such information may be collected by the site and included in its customer database.

If a subscriber sends any personal communication or correspondence, by any means, to the site, or any of its employees, agents or representatives, the site may collect any information regarding that communication and include that information in its customer database.

The site may also automatically collect traffic and click-through data as well as information regarding the online behavior of subscribers by the use of "cookies" or other programming means - any information about subscribers collected by the site through the use ofcookies or other programming means will generally not be associable to the specific user in any way.

Use of Personal Subscriber Information.

By the subscriber's use of the site, the subscriber expressly agrees that the site may use any personal information that has beenprovided by the subscriber or that has been collected by the site about the subscriber for any purpose, including without limitation, technical, administration, research and development, customer administration, marketing, trading in personal data, age verification, promotional and advertising use by the site or third parties authorized to use the information by the site.

By the subscriber's use of the site, the subscriber expressly agrees that the site may, in its sole discretion share, disclose, transfer, rent, license or sell any of the personal information about subscribers that it has gathered or collected with affiliated or unaffiliated third parties.

Please note that personal information about a subscriber may be collected by a third-party web service provider that has an advertising banner or link on the site.

The site is not responsible or liable for the use of any information that a subscriber may provide, or that is gathered by third-party websites that have banner ads or links on the site. This site does not control, monitor or endorse the information gathering practices or privacy policies of any of those third-party websites.

Whenever applicable, each subscriber should seek to read the privacy policy of any third-party website provider that has an advertising banner, advertises or has a link on the site.
